Privacy Policy of **Metro Parent**
==================================

Metro Parent collects some Personal Data from its Users.

This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.

Owner and Data Controller
-------------------------

Metro Parent Media Group  
22041 Woodward Ave  
Ferndale, MI 48220  
United States

**Owner contact email:** mpweb@metroparent.com

Types of Data collected
-----------------------

Among the types of Personal Data that Metro Parent collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies; Usage Data; email address; first name; last name; username.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using Metro Parent.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by Metro Parent is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for Metro Parent to provide its services. In cases where Metro Parent specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools — by Metro Parent or by the owners of third-party services used by Metro Parent serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through Metro Parent.

Mode and place of processing the Data
-------------------------------------

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of Metro Parent (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.  
  
Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

### Retention time

Unless specified otherwise in this document, Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for and may be retained for longer due to applicable legal obligation or based on the Users’ consent.

The purposes of processing
--------------------------

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Service, comply with its legal obligations, respond to enforcement requests, protect its rights and interests (or those of its Users or third parties), detect any malicious or fraudulent activity, as well as the following: Analytics, Tag Management, Remarketing and behavioral targeting, Displaying content from external platforms, Contacting the User, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Content commenting, Managing contacts and sending messages, SPAM protection, Advertising, Platform services and hosting and User database management.

For specific information about the Personal Data used for each purpose, the User may refer to the section “Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data”.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
-------------------------------------------------------

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

* ### Advertising
    
    This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes. These communications are displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on Metro Parent, possibly based on User interests.  
    This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
    Some of the services listed below may use Trackers to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside Metro Parent. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
    Services of this kind usually offer the possibility to opt out of such tracking. In addition to any opt-out feature offered by any of the services below, Users may learn more on how to generally opt out of interest-based advertising within the dedicated section "How to opt-out of interest-based advertising" in this document.
    
    #### Broadstreet Ads (Broadstreet Ads, Inc.)
    
    Broadstreet Ads is an advertising service provided by Broadstreet Ads, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://broadstreetads.com/privacy-policy/).
    
    #### Meta ads conversion tracking (Meta pixel) (Meta Platforms, Inc.)
    
    Meta ads conversion tracking (Meta pixel) is an analytics service provided by Meta Platforms, Inc. that connects data from the Meta Audience Network with actions performed on Metro Parent. The Meta pixel tracks conversions that can be attributed to ads on Facebook, Instagram and Meta Audience Network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Trackers; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt out](https://www.facebook.com/adpreferences/ad_settings).
    
* ### Analytics
    
    The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
    
    #### Google Analytics (Universal Analytics) (Google Inc.)
    
    Google Analytics (Universal Analytics) is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of Metro Parent, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
    Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
    
    In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult [Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
    
    #### HubSpot Analytics (HubSpot, Inc.)
    
    HubSpot Analytics is an analytics service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy) – [Opt Out](mailto:privacy@hubspot.com) .
    
* ### Contacting the User
    
    #### Contact form (Metro Parent)
    
    By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes Metro Parent to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; first name; last name.
    
    #### Mailing list or newsletter (Metro Parent)
    
    By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning Metro Parent. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to Metro Parent or after making a purchase.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; first name; last name.
    
* ### Content commenting
    
    Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of Metro Parent.  
    Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
    If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.
    
    #### Facebook Comments (Facebook, Inc.)
    
    Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook, Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).
    
* ### Displaying content from external platforms
    
    This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of Metro Parent and interact with them.  
    This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.
    
    #### YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)
    
    YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).
    
    #### Gravatar (Automattic Inc.)
    
    Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
    Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter's email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar - even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
    
    #### Google Fonts (Google Inc.)
    
    Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/).
    
    #### Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)
    
    Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/).
    
    #### SoundCloud widget (SoundCloud Limited)
    
    Soundcloud is an audio content delivery service provided by SoundCloud Limited that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: Germany – [Privacy Policy](https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy).
    
    #### Issuu widget (Issuu, Inc)
    
    Issuu is a digital content visualization service provided by Issuu, Inc. that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://issuu.com/legal/privacy).
    
    #### Spotify widget (Spotify AB)
    
    Spotify is an audio content delivery service provided by Spotify AB that allows Metro Parent to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: Sweden – [Privacy Policy](https://www.spotify.com/us/legal/privacy-policy/).
    
* ### Hosting and backend infrastructure
    
    This type of service has the purpose of hosting Data and files that enable Metro Parent to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of Metro Parent. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.
    
    #### Amazon Web Services (AWS) (Amazon Web Services, Inc.)
    
    Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a hosting and backend service provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/).
    
* ### Managing contacts and sending messages
    
    This type of service makes it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User.  
    These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message.
    
    #### Sendgrid (Sendgrid)
    
    Sendgrid is an email address management and message sending service provided by Sendgrid Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; username.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://sendgrid.com/privacy).
    
    #### HubSpot Email (HubSpot, Inc.)
    
    HubSpot Email is an email address management and message sending service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: email address; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy).
    
* ### Platform services and hosting
    
    These services have the purpose of hosting and running key components of Metro Parent, therefore allowing the provision of Metro Parent from within a unified platform. Such platforms provide a wide range of tools to the Owner – e.g. analytics, user registration, commenting, database management, e-commerce, payment processing – that imply the collection and handling of Personal Data.  
    Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.
    
    #### WordPress.com (Automattic Inc.)
    
    WordPress.com is a platform provided by Automattic Inc. that allows the Owner to build, run and host Metro Parent.
    
    Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
    
* ### Remarketing and behavioral targeting
    
    This type of service allows Metro Parent and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of Metro Parent by the User.  
    This activity is facilitated by tracking Usage Data and by using Trackers to collect information which is then transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.  
    Some services offer a remarketing option based on email address lists.  
    In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services below, Users may opt out by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).
    
    **Users may also opt-out of certain advertising features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or ads settings in general**.
    
    #### Facebook Remarketing (Facebook, Inc.)
    
    Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of Metro Parent with the Facebook advertising network.
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
    
    #### Google Ads Remarketing (Google LLC)
    
    Google Ads Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google LLC that connects the activity of Metro Parent with the Google Ads advertising network and the DoubleClick Cookie.
    
    Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
    #### Remarketing with Google Analytics (Google LLC)
    
    Remarketing with Google Analytics is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google LLC that connects the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its Trackers with the Google Ads advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.
    
    Personal Data processed: Tracker; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).
    
* ### SPAM protection
    
    This type of service analyzes the traffic of Metro Parent, potentially containing Users' Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.
    
    #### Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)
    
    Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.  
    The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).
    
    In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult [Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
    
    Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://business.safety.google/privacy/).
    
* ### Tag Management
    
    This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on Metro Parent in a centralized fashion.  
    This results in the Users' Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data.
    
    #### Google Tag Manager (Google LLC)
    
    Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC.
    
    Personal Data processed: Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
    
* ### User database management
    
    This type of service allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to Metro Parent, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks' profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving Metro Parent.  
    Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on Metro Parent.
    
    #### HubSpot CRM (HubSpot, Inc.)
    
    HubSpot CRM is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
    
    Personal Data processed: Trackers; Usage Data.
    
    Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy).

Information on opting out of interest-based advertising
-------------------------------------------------------

In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services listed in this document, Users may learn more on how to generally opt out of interest-based advertising within the dedicated section of the Cookie Policy.

Further information about the processing of Personal Data
---------------------------------------------------------

* ### The Service is not directed to children under the age of 13
    
    Users declare themselves to be adult according to their applicable legislation. Minors may use Metro Parent only with the assistance of a parent or guardian. Under no circumstance persons under the age of 13 may use Metro Parent.

Cookie Policy
-------------

Metro Parent uses Trackers. To learn more, Users may consult the [Cookie Policy](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/71210720/cookie-policy "Cookie Policy").

Further Information for Users
-----------------------------

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

* Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes.
* provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
* processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
* processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
* processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

### Further information about retention time

Unless specified otherwise in this document, Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for and may be retained for longer due to applicable legal obligation or based on the Users’ consent.

Therefore:

* Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
* Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to fulfil a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.  
  
Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right of access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

### The rights of Users based on the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following, to the extent permitted by law:

* **Withdraw their consent at any time.** Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
* **Object to processing of their Data.** Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent.
* **Access their Data.** Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
* **Verify and seek rectification.** Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
* **Restrict the processing of their Data.** Users have the right to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
* **Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.** Users have the right to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
* **Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.** Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance.
* **Lodge a complaint.** Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis for Data transfers abroad including to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

#### Details about the right to object to processing

**Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.**

**Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time, free of charge and without providing any justification. Where the User objects to processing for direct marketing purposes, the Personal Data will no longer be processed for such purposes. To learn whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.**

#### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. Such requests are free of charge and will be answered by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month, providing Users with the information required by law. Any rectification or erasure of Personal Data or restriction of processing will be communicated by the Owner to each recipient, if any, to whom the Personal Data has been disclosed unless this proves impossible or involves disproportionate effort. At the Users’ request, the Owner will inform them about those recipients.

Additional information about Data collection and processing
-----------------------------------------------------------

### Legal action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of Metro Parent or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, Metro Parent may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, Metro Parent and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with Metro Parent (System logs) or use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by notifying its Users on this page and possibly within Metro Parent and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.  
  
Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically through Metro Parent (or third-party services employed in Metro Parent), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use Metro Parent, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using Metro Parent who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

#### Data Subject

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Processor)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of Metro Parent. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of Metro Parent.

#### Metro Parent (or this Application)

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

#### Service

The service provided by Metro Parent as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

#### European Union (or EU)

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

#### Cookie

Cookies are Trackers consisting of small sets of data stored in the User's browser.

#### Tracker

Tracker indicates any technology - e.g Cookies, unique identifiers, web beacons, embedded scripts, e-tags and fingerprinting - that enables the tracking of Users, for example by accessing or storing information on the User’s device.

* * *

#### Legal information

This privacy policy relates solely to Metro Parent, if not stated otherwise within this document.

Latest update: April 30, 2024

This document has been created with the iubenda [Privacy and Cookie Policy Generator](https://www.iubenda.com/en/privacy-and-cookie-policy-generator). See also the [Terms and Conditions Generator](https://www.iubenda.com/en/terms-and-conditions-generator). [iubenda](https://www.iubenda.com/en/privacy-and-cookie-policy-generator) hosts this content and only collects [the Personal Data strictly necessary](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/65675001) for it to be provided.
